<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video on CG</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video on CG</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is a minor in college and do you need one?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-a-minor-in-college-and-do-you-need-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-a-minor-in-college-and-do-you-need-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As students pursue careers within a particular discipline, college majors have a considerable impact on their career paths and lives. College minors should be considered equally carefully by undergraduate students, according to experts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;College majors comprise structured coursework within an area of study chosen by the student. It is possible for students to take upwards of 30 hours of courses depending on their major and school. A minor, on the other hand, typically has six to seven courses requiring 18 credit hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where should I go to college? How to choose a “good” university</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-should-i-go-to-college-how-to-choose-a-good-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-should-i-go-to-college-how-to-choose-a-good-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;type-of-college&#34;&gt;Type of College&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Selecting a university where you will pursue your higher education is a big deal. This article is a guide to help you make that decision. The first thing to consider is the type of college you’d like to attend. The different types of colleges you can select from include; public or private colleges, for-profit colleges, 4-year or 2-year colleges, vocational training and career colleges, universities or community colleges, colleges with a special interest (single-sex colleges, specialized mission colleges, arts colleges or religion affiliated colleges) or liberal arts colleges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
