<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video on CG</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video on CG</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Should you even go to college? These questions will help you decide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/should-you-even-go-to-college-these-questions-will-help-you-decide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/should-you-even-go-to-college-these-questions-will-help-you-decide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks to ever-changing economic conditions, worsening student debt, rising costs, and uncertain political outlook for the foreseeable future, many students in the US are questioning the viability of attending college.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Though it&amp;rsquo;s true that college is the right decision for an always-narrowing scope of students, and alternatives are more viable than ever, it&amp;rsquo;s still a question that you must take seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Part of the process for evaluating whether you should go to knowledge is determining what your future career path will be and what your budget is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is a minor in college and do you need one?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-a-minor-in-college-and-do-you-need-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-a-minor-in-college-and-do-you-need-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As students pursue careers within a particular discipline, college majors have a considerable impact on their career paths and lives. College minors should be considered equally carefully by undergraduate students, according to experts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;College majors comprise structured coursework within an area of study chosen by the student. It is possible for students to take upwards of 30 hours of courses depending on their major and school. A minor, on the other hand, typically has six to seven courses requiring 18 credit hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What should you study in college? How to choose a major</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-should-you-study-in-college-how-to-choose-a-major/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-should-you-study-in-college-how-to-choose-a-major/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What you choose to study in college can make or break your career life. Choose the wrong course combination and you’ll likely end up with an unbearably hard struggle during your academic years. And even if you’re lucky to complete the course, chances are that you’ll end up disliking your eventual career only to end up struggling with performance and all kinds of job satisfaction-related complaints.&#xA;Long story short, the choice of what to study in college should be informed based on several factors key among them:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where should I go to college? How to choose a “good” university</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-should-i-go-to-college-how-to-choose-a-good-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-should-i-go-to-college-how-to-choose-a-good-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;type-of-college&#34;&gt;Type of College&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Selecting a university where you will pursue your higher education is a big deal. This article is a guide to help you make that decision. The first thing to consider is the type of college you’d like to attend. The different types of colleges you can select from include; public or private colleges, for-profit colleges, 4-year or 2-year colleges, vocational training and career colleges, universities or community colleges, colleges with a special interest (single-sex colleges, specialized mission colleges, arts colleges or religion affiliated colleges) or liberal arts colleges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
