<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on CG</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/basics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on CG</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 12:09:17 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What should you study in college? How to choose a major (without regretting it later)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-should-you-study-in-college-how-to-choose-a-major/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 12:09:17 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-should-you-study-in-college-how-to-choose-a-major/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Choosing a college major sounds simple on paper. Pick something. Study it. Graduate. Move on with life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In reality? It’s one of the most stressful decisions students face.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You’re often asked to decide &lt;em&gt;what you want to do with your life&lt;/em&gt; before you’ve even had a real job. Advice comes from everywhere—parents, teachers, friends, TikTok, random rankings online—and most of it contradicts itself. One person says “follow your passion.” Another says “pick something practical.” Someone else says your major doesn’t matter at all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I go to college? A question-first guide for high school students</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/should-you-even-go-to-college-these-questions-will-help-you-decide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 09:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/should-you-even-go-to-college-these-questions-will-help-you-decide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-isnt-a-yes-or-no-question&#34;&gt;This Isn’t a Yes-or-No Question&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Should I go to college?” sounds like a simple question. It isn’t.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For years, students have been told that college is the &lt;em&gt;default&lt;/em&gt; path. Go to class, get good grades, apply, enroll, and everything will work out. If you don’t go, something must be wrong. That story is everywhere — in schools, in families, in movies, even in casual conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But here’s the honest truth: college isn’t automatically good or bad. It’s a tool. And like any tool, it only works well if it fits the person using it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
